



Greg Morris

4 Ince Close

Manchester

M20 3GJ

07789 656 348

greg.morris85@gmail.com



HTML5 JavaScript

NextJS

TypeScript

CSS/SASS

PHP

React

GraphQL

KeystoneJS

WordPress

Laravel Eleventy

Films VR

Tabletop RPGs

ΑI

Video Games

Summary

Self-taught Web Developer (with a curious love of vaporwave) with 7 years of industry experience, specializing in creating user-friendly, responsive websites. Has proven ability to design and build complete web applications, managing both frontend aesthetics and backend structures. Establishes and develops projects to completion within stringent constraints and best practice. Demonstrates proficiency in learning new technologies and procedures, coupled with a proactive approach to identifying and implementing potential improvements to enhance current projects.

Education

University of Lincoln

2003 - 2006

Diploma of Higher Education



Professional Experience

March 2023 - Current Carma

Web Developer

- Joined as primary developer in a start-up environment to maintain and improve the company's site and services
- Solely developed new user Dashboard and Service Backend from MVP and into production using a NextJS client with a KeystoneJS backend
- Guided and collaborated with contracted developers to migrate data and functionality from the Bubble WYSIWYG service to the new Dashboard
- Developing new features and maintaining the Dashboard, working closely with the owner to provide enagaging services and support to our
- Mentoring our web development apprentice during thier placement

Sept 2021 - March 2023 **Electric Circus**

Web Developer

- Worked primarily as a Frontend developer on a small development team and grew my skills to cover backend development with Laravel
- Created custom client sites with Cornerstone LMS using Laravel and Nova CMS
- Collaborated closely with designers to create unique, tailored client websites in Wordpress
- Ensured current client WordPress sites are maintained and updated as necessary

March 2018 - Sept 2021 Volcanic

Frontend Web Developer

- Worked as part of the Frontend Team to deliver high quality recruitment websites to global clients
- Identified a need for and worked with management to create a dedicated Support Developers Team
- Headed the Support Developers Team that handled day to day change requests, site issues and emergency fixes for current clients
 - Resulted in less pressure on other developers, improving the quality of work put out by other departments.
 - Greatly increased customer satisfaction through reduced response times and a better quality of service for support issues
- Coached new hires and current staff joining the newly created team

Dec 2016 - March 2018 CDL

Frontend Web Developer

- Worked as part of a team creating and maintaining websites and back-ends for many of the UK's top insurance companies.
- Developed change requests sent by clients to alter the appearance or functionality of their insurance websites.
- Ensured all clients' sites meet the currently enforced FCA regulatory guidelines.
- Updated sites to newer versions of CDL's JSP core code.
- Liaised with clients to ensure their requests are carried out to their specification and their satisfaction.
- Provided follow-up support for any errors or oversights discovered after a website had gone live and ensured a swift resolution with minimal downtime for the customer.

